manulife financial corporation is a
leading international financial services
group that helps people make their
decisions easier and lives better
with our global headquarters in toronto
canada we operate as manulife across our
offices in canada asia and europe and
primarily as john hancock in the united
states
manulife and john hancock are
internationally recognized brands which
have stood for financial strength and
integrity for more than 155 years
we have 1.3 trillion canadian dollars
worth of assets under management over
118 agents and thousands of distribution
partners with more than 37 000 employees
serving more than 30 million customers
worldwide operating in 13 markets in
asia
established in 1980 manulife singapore
provides insurance retirement and wealth
management
our diverse presence is bolstered by our
multi-channel distribution network which
is made up of our agency force bank
partners and financial advisory firm
in 2016 we embarked on a 15-year bank
assurance partnership with dbs bank
across four markets in asia singapore
hong kong indonesia and china the
relationship which significantly
strengthened our distribution
capabilities has seen us work
successfully together with dbs to be the
number one bank assurer in singapore
providing a comprehensive suite of
insurance solutions and self-directed
digital propositions to meet the
protection savings and retirement needs
of our customers across asia
our selection of protection and
investment products are designed to meet
different needs across every life stage
life financial protection for you and
your family in times of need
health financial support for your
medical and hospital care
saving discipline financial planning to
make your dreams a reality
investment investment opportunities to
achieve your financial goals
signature premium suite of solutions to
grow and protect your legacy
digital a diverse range of insurance
policies online to meet specific needs
get better health and be rewarded with
every step you take
manulife move is a customer rewards
program designed to reward you for every
move you make
enjoy today knowing tomorrow is covered
that's
every day
better
[Music]